Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Administration and Finance Committee, 1900 -- 2020; UA003.004; 13.0 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes; 22 Digital Object(s) 22 zip files containing 518 files.; 717.69 Megabytes
  - Working Papers, 1960 -- 2000; UA003.004.002
    - Administration and Finance Committee, November 5, 1993; UA003.004.060.00005 (Box 60)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, February 9, 1996; UA003.004.091.00012 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, May 17, 1996; UA003.004.091.00013 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, November 1, 1996; UA003.004.091.00014 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, February 7, 1997; UA003.004.091.00015 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, May 16, 1997; UA003.004.091.00016 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, November 7, 1997; UA003.004.091.00017 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, February 6, 1998; UA003.004.091.00018 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, March 18, 1998; UA003.004.091.00019 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, May 15, 1998; UA003.004.091.00020 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, September 29, 1998; UA003.004.091.00021 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, November 6, 1998; UA003.004.091.00022 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, February 5, 1999; UA003.004.091.00023 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, May 21, 1999; UA003.004.091.00024 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, September 21, 1999; UA003.004.091.00025 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, November 6, 1999; UA003.004.091.00026 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, February 11, 2000; UA003.004.091.00027 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, May 19, 2000; UA003.004.091.00028 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, September 26, 2000; UA003.004.091.00029 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, November 3, 2000; UA003.004.091.00030 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, Working Papers, September 1, 1995; UA003.004.102.00001 (Box 102)
    - Administration and Finance Committee, Working Papers, November 3, 1995; UA003.004.102.00002 (Box 102)
    - Omidyar-Tufts Microfinance Fund and Administration and Finance Committee, Working Papers, 2005 -- 2010; UA003.004.128; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 128, Folder 29 - 47)
  - Administration and finance files, 2000-2016; UA003.004.00001; 268 Digital Object(s); 0.44 Gigabytes
  - Administration and Finance committee files, 2017; UA003.004.00003; 28 Digital Object(s); 28.2 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance committee files, 2017; UA003.004.00004; 16 Digital Object(s); 9.05 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance committee files, 2017; UA003.004.00005; 4 Digital Object(s); 2.42 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance committee files, 2017; UA003.004.00006; 20 Digital Object(s); 28.4 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance committee files, 2018; UA003.004.00007; 15 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance committee files, 2018; UA003.004.00008; 20 Digital Object(s); 31.8 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, special session, 2018-07-11; UA003.004.00009; 6 Digital Object(s); 4.89 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, special session, 2018-10-01; UA003.004.00010; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.76 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2018-11-02; UA003.004.00011; 16 Digital Object(s); 40.06 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2019-02-08; UA003.004.00012; 17 Digital Object(s); 13.47 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, special session, 2019-03-26; UA003.004.00013; 6 Digital Object(s); 5.62 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, ballot vote, 2019-05-01; UA003.004.00014; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.24 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2019-05-17; UA003.004.00015; 19 Digital Object(s); 22.59 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, regular session, 2019 November 01; UA003.002322; 38 Megabytes 19 files
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 February 07; UA003.002353; 16.32 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 May 08; UA003.002354; 2.07 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 May 15; UA003.002355; 7.11 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 June 16; UA003.002356; 4.27 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 July 31; UA003.002357; 3.76 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 September 22; UA003.002358; 3.4 Megabytes
  - Administration and Finance Committee files, 2020 November 06; UA003.002359; 10.76 Megabytes
- Audit Committee, 1976 -- 2020; UA003.005; 2.4 Linear Feet; 17 Digital Object(s) 17 zip files containing 360 files.; .44 Gigabytes
  This series contains material from Tufts University's Audit Committee from 1976 to 2000. These materials are arranged in chronological order by committee meeting date. Folders contain meeting announcements, agendas, minutes, letters, budgets, and audit reports.
  This committee considers and advises the Board and the Executive Committee with respect to the corporation's internal audit procedures, employment of independent certified public accountants, and all matters in connection with independent audits and the formulation of policies or procedures for the avoidance of Trustee conflict of interest. The Audit Committee was created in 1975.
  - Audit Committee, March 19, 1976; UA003.005.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, September 15, 1976; UA003.005.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, December 15, 1976; UA003.005.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, March 25, 1977; UA003.005.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, September 21, 1977; UA003.005.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, February 24, 1978; UA003.005.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 11, 1978; UA003.005.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, February 23, 1979; UA003.005.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 11, 1979; UA003.005.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 2, 1979; UA003.005.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, February 22, 1980; UA003.005.064.00011 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 9, 1980; UA003.005.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, July 9, 1980; UA003.005.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 30, 1980; UA003.005.064.00014 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, February 27, 1981; UA003.005.064.00015 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 23, 1981; UA003.005.064.00016 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 29, 1982; UA003.005.064.00017 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 5, 1982; UA003.005.064.00019 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 8, 1983; UA003.005.064.00020 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 15, 1983; UA003.005.064.00021 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 26, 1983; UA003.005.064.00022 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 26, 1983; UA003.005.064.00023 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 25, 1984; UA003.005.064.00024 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 31, 1984; UA003.005.064.00025 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 2, 1980; UA003.005.064.00026 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 8, 1985; UA003.005.064.00027 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 30, 1986; UA003.005.064.00028 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 14, 1986; UA003.005.064.00029 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 15, 1987; UA003.005.064.00030 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 27, 1987; UA003.005.064.00031 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 20, 1988; UA003.005.064.00032 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 5, 1988; UA003.005.064.00033 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 25, 1988; UA003.005.064.00034 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 25, 1989; UA003.005.064.00035 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 23, 1990; UA003.005.064.00036 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 24, 1989; UA003.005.064.00037 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 24, 1990; UA003.005.064.00038 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, October 23, 1990; UA003.005.064.00039 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 23, 1991; UA003.005.064.00040 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, April 23, 1991; UA003.005.064.00041 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 1, 1991; UA003.005.064.00042 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 1, 1991; UA003.005.064.00043 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 21, 1993; UA003.005.064.00044 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 5, 1993; UA003.005.064.00045 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 5, 1994; UA003.005.064.00046 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 15, 1992; UA003.005.064.00047 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 6, 1992; UA003.005.064.00048 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 4, 1994; UA003.005.064.00049 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, May 19, 1995; UA003.005.064.00050 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, November 3, 1995; UA003.005.064.00051 (Box 64)
  - Audit Committee, February 9, 1996; UA003.005.091.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, May 17, 1996; UA003.005.091.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, November 1, 1996; UA003.005.091.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, May 16, 1997; UA003.005.091.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, November 7, 1997; UA003.005.091.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, December 11, 1997; UA003.005.091.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, May 15, 1998; UA003.005.091.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, November 6, 1998; UA003.005.091.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, May 21, 1999; UA003.005.091.00009 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, November 5, 1999; UA003.005.091.00010 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit Committee, November 3, 2000; UA003.005.091.00011 (Box UA003 Shared 6)
  - Audit committee working files, 2007 -- 2010; UA003.005.129; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 129, Folder 16 - 25)
  - Audit files, 2004-2016; UA003.005.00001; 155 Digital Object(s); 0.27 Gigabytes
  - Audit committee files, 2017; UA003.005.00003; 18 Digital Object(s); 16.1 Megabytes
  - Audit committee files, 2017; UA003.005.00004; 8 Digital Object(s); 5.6 Megabytes
  - Audit committee files, 2017; UA003.005.00005; 14 Digital Object(s); 17.2 Megabytes
  - Audit committee files, 2018; UA003.005.00006; 16 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes
  - Audit committee files, 2018; UA003.005.00007; 17 Digital Object(s); 14.6 Megabytes
  - Audit committee files, 2018; UA003.005.00008; 7 Digital Object(s); 6.91 Megabytes
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2018-05-18; UA003.005.00009; 17 Digital Object(s); 14.65 Megabytes
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2018-11-02; UA003.005.00010; 14 Digital Object(s); 22.87 Megabytes
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2019-02-13; UA003.005.00011; 13 Digital Object(s); 18.05 Megabytes
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, special session, 2019-03-26; UA003.005.00012; 9 Digital Object(s); 9.06 Megabytes
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2019-05-17; UA003.005.00013; 15 Digital Object(s); 14.02 Megabytes
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, regular session, 2019 November 01; UA003.002323; 18.9 Megabytes 10 files
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2020 February 07; UA003.002360; 14.46 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 15 files.
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2020 May 14; UA003.002361; 14.06 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2020 August 04; UA003.002362; 1.93 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Audit, Risk and Compliance Committee files, 2020 November 05; UA003.002363; 14.09 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 13 files.
- Honorary Degree Committee working papers and subject files, 1858 -- 2020; UA003.006; 2.4 Linear Feet; 16 Digital Object(s) 16 zip files containing 242 files; 291.37 Megabytes
  This series contains material related to Tufts University Honorary Degrees. This material includes working papers from the Honorary Degree Committee, files compiled by Russell Miller, and Office of the Board of Trustees office files. Working papers are arranged in chronological order by committee meeting date. Folders contain announcements, agendas, minutes, lists of recommended honorary degree candidates and correspondence between HD committee and nominated candidates.
  - Honorary Degrees: Awarded, 1858 -- 1988; UA003.006.045.00001 (Box 45)
    Russell Miller file
  - Honorary Degrees: Recommended (A-L), 1921 -- 1949; UA003.006.045.00002 (Box 45)
  - Honorary Degrees: Recommended (M-Z), 1909 -- 1965; UA003.006.045.00003 (Box 45)
  - Honorary Degrees: Recommended, NOT Awarded, 1927 -- 1937; UA003.006.045.00004 (Box 45)
  - Honorary Degrees: Not Recommended, 1911 -- 1937; UA003.006.045.00005 (Box 45)
  - Honoris Causa Admissi - book listing honorary degrees, 1875 -- 1917; UA003.006.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree process backup materials [Binder], 1995 -- 1996; UA003.006.045.00007 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree eligible pool and bios [Binder] 1 of 3, 1999; UA003.006.045.00008 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree eligible pool and bios [Binder] 2 of 3, 1999; UA003.006.045.00009 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree eligible pool and bios [Binder] 3 of 3, 1999; UA003.006.045.00010 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree nominations [Binder] 1 of 4, 1999 -- 2000; UA003.006.045.00011 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree nominations [Binder] 2 of 4, 1999 -- 2000; UA003.006.045.00012 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree nominations [Binder] 3 of 4, 1999 -- 2000; UA003.006.045.00013 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree nominations [Binder] 4 of 4, 1999 -- 2000; UA003.006.045.00014 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degrees [Binder] 1 of 2, 2000 -- 2001; UA003.006.045.00015 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degrees [Binder] 2 of 2, 2000 -- 2001; UA003.006.045.00016 (Box 45)
  - [Honorary Degree committee], 2001; UA003.006.045.00017 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree candidates [Binder] 1 of 3, 2001; UA003.006.045.00018 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree candidates [Binder] 2 of 3, 2001; UA003.006.045.00019 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree candidates [Binder] 3 of 3, 2001; UA003.006.045.00020 (Box 45)
  - Honorary degree nominees (Last Updated April 1, 2003) [Binder], 2002 -- 2003; UA003.006.045.00021 (Box 45)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1985 -- 1986; UA003.006.088.00001 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Candidates, 1986 -- 1987; UA003.006.088.00002 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Candidates, 1987 -- 1988; UA003.006.088.00003 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Recommendations, 1988 -- 1989; UA003.006.088.00004 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Nominations, 1989 -- 1990; UA003.006.088.00005 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, Working Papers, February 10, 1995; UA003.006.088.00006 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, Working Papers, May 9, 1995; UA003.006.088.00007 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee (LJD Mnts), May 20, 1995; UA003.006.088.00008 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, Working Papers, November 3, 1995; UA003.006.088.00009 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, February 6, 1996; UA003.006.088.00010 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, November 2, 1996; UA003.006.088.00011 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, February 7, 1997; UA003.006.088.00012 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, March 18, 1997; UA003.006.088.00013 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, May 16, 1997; UA003.006.088.00014 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, October 2, 1997; UA003.006.088.00015 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, February 6, 1998; UA003.006.088.00016 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, March 17, 1998; UA003.006.088.00017 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, September 9, 1998; UA003.006.088.00018 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, October 20, 1998; UA003.006.088.00019 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, January 8, 1999; UA003.006.088.00020 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, January 12, 1999; UA003.006.088.00021 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, February 26, 1999; UA003.006.088.00022 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, May 21, 1999; UA003.006.088.00023 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, October 7, 1999; UA003.006.088.00024 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, October 29, 1999; UA003.006.088.00025 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, February 11, 2000; UA003.006.088.00026 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, March 14, 2000; UA003.006.088.00027 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, September 25, 2000; UA003.006.088.00028 (Box 88)
  - Honorary Degree Committee working papers, 2007 -- 2010; UA003.006.130; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 130, Folder 37 - 47)
  - Honorary degree committee files, 2004-2016; UA003.006.00001; 140 Digital Object(s); 0.2 Gigabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2016; UA003.006.00002; 7 Digital Object(s); .007 Gigabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2017; UA003.006.00003; 7 Digital Object(s); 6.22 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2017; UA003.006.00004; 7 Digital Object(s); 7.5 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2017; UA003.006.00005; 6 Digital Object(s); 10.8 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2017; UA003.006.00006; 7 Digital Object(s); 7.98 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2018; UA003.006.00007; 5 Digital Object(s); 4.58 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree committee files, 2018; UA003.006.00008; 8 Digital Object(s); 7.46 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2018-11-02; UA003.006.00009; 7 Digital Object(s); 7.09 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2019-02-06; UA003.006.00010; 8 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2019-05-17; UA003.006.00011; 7 Digital Object(s); 8.82 Megabytes
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, regular session, 2019 November 01; UA003.002335; 8.5 Megabytes 7 files
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2020 February 07; UA003.002392; 7.2 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2020 February 28; UA003.002393; 2.6 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2020 May 11; UA003.002394; 5.14 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Honorary Degree Committee files, 2020 November 02; UA003.002395; 6.43 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
- Committee on Trusteeship, 1857 -- 2020; UA003.007; 4.7 Linear Feet; 17 Digital Object(s) 17 zip files containing 501 files.; 560.43 Megabytes
  This series contains materials from the Committee on Trusteeship from 1880 to 2000. These materials are arranged in chronological order by committee meeting date. Folders contain announcements, agendas, and minutes. There is also a small section of this series that includes six photographs of trustees from events between 1959 to 1967.
  - Bell, W. Douglas (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - Cardozo, Anthony Dej (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00003 (Box 28)
  - Chayet, Neil L. A'1960 (Trustee), 1968 -- 1984; UA003.007.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - Gilbert, Carl J. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00005 (Box 28)
  - Goldberg, Carol (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - Duncan, Christopher (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - Hallowell, Burton C. (former Trustee and President), UA003.007.028.00008 (Box 28)
  - Heneghan, John J. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00009 (Box 28)
  - Howard, James B. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00010 (Box 28)
  - MacPhie, Etta P. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00011 (Box 28)
  - Marvin, Usrula Bailey (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00012 (Box 28)
  - Reynolds, Joel W. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00013 (Box 28)
  - Segal, Maurice S. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00014 (Box 28)
  - Thompson, Cameron S. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00015 (Box 28)
  - Weiant, Elizabeth (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00016 (Box 28)
  - White, Edward A. (Trustee), UA003.007.028.00017 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1863-1932, UA003.007.031.00001 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence, 1933 -- 1973; UA003.007.031.00002 (Box 31)
  - 1967-86, 1967 -- 1986; UA003.007.031.00003 (Box 31)
  - 1907-79, 1907 -- 1979; UA003.007.031.00004 (Box 31)
  - 1903-06, 1903 -- 1906; UA003.007.031.00005 (Box 31)
  - Board of Overseers, UA003.007.031.00006 (Box 31)
  - Benefactors: General, UA003.007.031.00007 (Box 31)
  - Benefactors: Olney Arnold, UA003.007.031.00008 (Box 31)
  - Benefactors: Elbridge Rust, UA003.007.033.00001 (Box 33)
  - Dinner for Faculty (1959-63), 1959 -- 1963; UA003.007.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - Dinner for Faculty (1951-59), 1951 -- 1959; UA003.007.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - Dinner for Faculty (1960-62), 1960 -- 1962; UA003.007.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - Dinner for Faculty (1963-67), 1963 -- 1967; UA003.007.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - Seal and Colors, UA003.007.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - State Aid, UA003.007.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - Inactive Trustees: Boyd (confidential), UA003.007.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - Inactive Trustees: Fobert, UA003.007.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - Inactive Trustees: Bush, UA003.007.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - Inactive Trustees: Carmichael (confidential), UA003.007.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - Inactive Trustees: Djerf (confidential), UA003.007.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - Inactive Trustees: Howie, UA003.007.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - Inactive Trustees: Williams (confidential), UA003.007.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - Former Trustees (confidential), UA003.007.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - Faculty workloads (confidential), UA003.007.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - Early Documents, Examining Committee, UA003.007.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Faculty Establishments (confidential), UA003.007.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Tuition Payment Plan (confidential), UA003.007.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Early Documents, Publicity, UA003.007.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Early Documents, President's Reports on Departments, UA003.007.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Executive Committee, 1857 -- 1879; UA003.007.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Early Documents (1880-89), Executive Committee, 1880 -- 1889; UA003.007.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - Executive Committee, 1890 -- 1896; UA003.007.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - Executive Committee, 1896-1900, UA003.007.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - Early Documents 1901-11, Executive Committee, 1901 -- 1911; UA003.007.048.00004 (Box 48)
  - Executive Committee, 1912 -- 1921; UA003.007.048.00005 (Box 48)
  - Trustees Photos, 1959 -- 1963; UA003.007.078.00001 (Box 78)
    Black and white photographic prints, mainly taken for promotional purposes, of the Board of Trustees and individual members in the 1950's and 1960's.
  - Trustees Photgraphs, 1954 -- 1965; UA003.007.078.00002 (Box 78)
  - Trusteeship Committee, February 9, 1996; UA003.007.084.00010 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, September 10, 1996; UA003.007.084.00011 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, January 7, 1997; UA003.007.084.00012 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, March 4, 1997; UA003.007.084.00013 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, May 16, 1997; UA003.007.084.00014 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, August 11, 1997; UA003.007.084.00015 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, March 3, 1998; UA003.007.084.00016 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, August 12, 1998; UA003.007.084.00017 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, March 2, 1999; UA003.007.084.00018 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, March 5, 1999; UA003.007.084.00019 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, August 12, 1999; UA003.007.084.00020 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, May 15, 2000; UA003.007.084.00021 (Box UA003 Shared 2)
  - Trusteeship Committee, September 21, 2000; UA003.007.084.00022 (Box UA003 Shared 2)